http://www.accubar.com/privacy-policy/

Welcome to the Privacy Policy of
AccuBar. AccuBar, Inc. (1301 Dove Street, Suite 300, Newport Beach, CA, 92660 United States) (“ AccuBar ”, “Company” “we” or “us”) respects your privacy and makes every effort to protect it.When you are visiting the
AccuBar Website or using the
AccuBar System, we may collect information that is considered personally identifiable (“personal data”) in certain jurisdictions.
AccuBar may also receive information about you from other sources, including trade organizations and contact directories provided to
AccuBar. AccuBar therefore publishes this privacy statement so that you can become acquainted with the way in which your personal data are collected and processed.Our privacy policy is divided in 3 segments:You are visiting the AccuBar WebsiteYou are using the AccuBar SystemGeneral informationCookies1. You are visiting the Accubar WebsiteAt different places throughout the AccuBar Website you can provide your contact details (e.g. completion of contact form, subscription to our newsletter, etc.) to AccuBar.AccuBar is responsible for the processing of the personal data that it receives via the website (“controller”).We will only process your personal data:In order to execute an agreement with you, i.e. in order to handle and answer your question and/or to send you our newsletter,When the processing is necessary to meet our legal obligations,When the processing is necessary for the protection of our legitimate interests, such as ensuring and improving the proper functioning and services of
AccuBar.2. You are using the
Accubar SystemThe company that offers you the use of the AccuBar System is responsible for the processing of your personal data via the AccuBar System (“controller”), which means that it determines the purpose and means for processing your personal data and that it is the primary responsible for ensuring that this processing is done in a legal, transparent and secure manner.The AccuBar System is developed and managed by AccuBar and in this respect, AccuBar has been appointed by the controller to process your personal data on its behalf and strictly in accordance with its instructions (“processor”).With respect to the AccuBar System, your personal data is only processed:In order to be able to provide you with a user account and allow you to us the AccuBar System, on the legal basis of our agreement with the controller and on the basis of your consent with this privacy policy,When the processing is necessary to meet our legal obligations,When the processing is necessary for the protection of our legitimate interests, such as ensuring and improving the proper functioning and services of AccuBar3. General information3.1. Whom do we share your personal data with?AccuBar may engage sub-contractors with respect to the processing of
your personal data (e.g. cloud storage providers, IT service providers, etc.). AccuBar
ensures to only engage sub-contractors providing sufficient guarantees towards
the lawful processing and security of your personal data.AccuBar may share your Personal Data with any entities affiliated to AccuBar.
We may also need to transfer your personal data to other recipients such as
public authorities, enforcement authorities, public prosecutors and courts, our
attorneys, advisors or other services providers, auditors or other third
parties, if we estimate in good faith that such disclosure is reasonably
necessary or useful (e.g. in order for us to comply with a legal obligation or
procedure, in the context of a merger, acquisition or reorganization of our
company or group, to broaden or improve our activities, to protect our rights
and interests or the security and safety of our organization, our
infrastructure, our activities, our clients, partners or the public), fully
taking into account our obligations under the applicable personal data
protection laws.In this respect, AccuBar will transfer your Personal Data across
borders. For transfers outside of the European
Economic Area, AccuBar will ensure an adequacy decision by the European
Commission is in place for the recipient country or organisation, or that
appropriate or suitable safeguards are in place, a copy of which can be
obtained by contacting AccuBar (see contact details below).3.2. Your rights with respect to your personal dataYou may
choose to not provide certain personal data when visiting the AccuBar Website
or using the AccuBar System; however, this may limit or restrict your ability
to use the AccuBar Website and the AccuBar System and ability to take advantage
of many AccuBar features.By
contacting us (see our contact details below) or the company that offers you the use of the AccuBar System, you may,
at any time request:confirmation as to whether or not personal
data concerning you are being processed by us and, where that is the case, you
may request access to or receipt of your personal data;to rectify inaccurate personal data
concerning you;to complete incomplete personal data
concerning you;to erase or to restrict the processing of
(certain) personal data relating to you;to transmit your personal data to another
controller or processor; andto cease the processing of your personal
data.Please
attach a copy of your identity card or passport to your request, enabling us to
verify your identity in order to prevent unlawful access to your personal data.
We will investigate whether it is feasible to respond to your request and
whether we are legally obliged to do so. We will give you written confirmation
about the chosen way forward.Via the AccuBar
System, you can also yourself update your personal data with respect to your AccuBar
System user account. It is your responsibility, and that of the company that offers you the use of the AccuBar System, to keep your
personal data accurate and up-to-date.If you are
of the opinion that your privacy rights have not been respected, you can also
file a complaint with the competent supervisory authority of your choice.You can exercise all rights described above without any charge. 3.3. Age requirements and usageThe
AccuBar System is not intended to be used by children and is a professional
business solution.  If you are under the age of 18, please do not use the AccuBar
System or disclose any personal information without involvement, supervision,
and permission of a parent or guardian.3.4. How do we safeguard data?We take reasonable technical and organizational measures to maintain the security and integrity of the collected personal data and prevent destruction, unauthorized access or use thereof, through generally accepted industry standard technologies and internal procedures.3.5. How long do we store your personal data?We will not store your personal data longer than is required or permitted by law to achieve the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including for evidence and anti-fraud reasons.3.6. Links to Third Party Websites?Certain links provided permit you to leave the AccuBar Website or the AccuBar System and enter non-AccuBar sites or services. Please note that our privacy notice does not apply for the processing of personal data done on these sites or services. We advise you to carefully read the privacy notices of the concerned sites or services to be informed about the processing of your personal data on such sites or services.3.7. Direct Marketing?If you have given us your consent, we may use your contact details for providing you commercial and/or non-commercial materials related to our current and/or future products and services by electronic means. You may withdraw your consent at any time by sending a written notice to privacy@birchstreetsystems.com or alternatively follow the instructions for removing yourself from the mailing list, which are available in the message transmitted to you.3.8. Changes to the Privacy Policy?The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the AccuBar Website and AccuBar System and any personal data collected with respect thereto. AccuBar reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently.4. CookiesWe use
cookies that are important for certain technical features of our website, like
logging into user accounts and implementing fixes and improvements to our
platform.These cookies:Enable behavior in our Products and/or Services that is tailored to the activity or preferences of a person visiting our siteHelp to diagnose and correct downtime, bugs, and errors in our code to ensure that our products are operating efficientlyIn general, we collect most data from you via form submission. However, there are cases when visiting our site and/or using our platforms in which we may receive certain information through the use of cookies. This data will generally not include personally identifying information about you.Unique identification tokensSession and language informationYou may prefer to disable cookies. You can do so by adjusting your cookie-settings. For more information in this respect, please consult the official websites of the browser you are using. If you choose to disable cookies, it is possible that (some functionalities on) the AccuBar Website and AccuBar System are no longer (fully) available to you.Advertising CookiesWe request your consent to use these cookies, and you can also opt-out at any time using tools listed below.AccuBar uses
cookies to give you a personalized and tailored user experience. Some of the
cookies we use are from third-party companies — such as Google Analytics,
AdRoll, Google Tag manager, Google AdWords conversion, Facebook pixel and
LinkedIn Insight tag — to provide us with web analytics and intelligence
regarding our websites. These companies use programming code to collect
information about your interactions with our websites, such as the pages you’ve
visited, the links you’ve clicked on, and the time you’ve spent on our
websites. This code is only active while you are on our website.These
cookies can help us serve relevant ads to you more effectively. AccuBar does
not serve any ads on our Site, however you may be served AccuBar Partner ads on
third party websites based on information collected about your prior usage and
viewing history on our Site.Data we collect for advertising purposes includes
usage of the site, IP address or mobile device location information (but only
to the extent you have enabled location tracking on your device), and may
include information from the AccuBar Partners we use to help deliver relevant
ads to you.For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many third-party providers, for information about how you can opt out of AccuBar’s collection and use of your information, please review “Your choices with respect to the collection and use of your information” below.We are collecting these cookies on our AccuBar Corporate website and not on the AccuBar application.SourcePersonal data collectedLinkedInThese types of cookies are used for retargeting, so we can show you relevant ads based on your activity on our Site after you leave it. Information collected includes an identifier, and sometimes your geolocation, device type, and IP address.FacebookThese types of cookies are used for retargeting, so we can show you relevant ads based on your activity on our Site after you leave it. Information collected includes an identifier, and sometimes your geolocation, device type, and IP address.AdRollThese types of cookies are for retargeting, so we can show you relevant ads based on your activity on our Site after you leave it. Information collected includes an identifier, and sometimes your geolocation, device type, and IP address.Google AnalyticsWe use Google Analytics to generate statistical data on how our visitors use our Site. We use IP masking to ensure that no personally identifiable information is collected.GoogleThese cookies are used to collect website statistics and track conversion rates. No personally identifiable information is collected.Your choices: To opt-out of advertising or analytic cookies you can also use the following tools:Type of cookieSourceOpt-Out toolsAdvertisingAdRollOpt-Out choiceGoogleOpt-Out choiceFacebookOpt-Out choiceLinked InOpt-Out choiceAnalytics and ResearchGoogle AnalyticsOpt-Out choiceAny Questions?If you have any questions
(or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are most welcome to send us
an email at privacy@birchstreetsystems.com.
Home | Products | Testimonials | Contact Us | Login U.S. Patent #6,616,037 © 2020 AccuBar. All rights reserved. HomeProductsTestimonialsLogin
